[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word refers to the ancient art of aerodynamically stabilizing arrows from materials, such as feathers or modern plastics.", "correct_answer": "Fletching", "incorrect_answers": ["Feathereting", "Cooperring", "Chancelloring"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 7 Virtues are:  Temperance, Charity, Diligence, Patience, Kindness, Humility, Chastity.  What are their opposites which are considered the 7 Deadly Sins?", "correct_answer": "Lust, Gluttony, Greed, Sloth, Wrath, Envy, Pride", "incorrect_answers": ["Greed, Anger, Envy, Jealousy, Conciet, Lust, Gluttony", "Greed, Anger, Envy, Jealousy, Dominance, Lust, Gluttony", "Carelessness, Anger, Envy, Jealousy, Conciet, Lust, Gluttony"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Male box turtles tend to be larger than females.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From which movie does this line come Its not unusual for a child to create an imaginary friend?", "correct_answer": "Hide and Seek", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sixth Sense", "Holes", "The Boogeyman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which town did Neal Page and Del Griffith board the train to Chicago in the film Planes, Trains  Automobiles?", "correct_answer": "Stubbville, KS", "incorrect_answers": ["Manhattan, KS", "Meriden, KS", "Lawrence, KS"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Blazing Saddles was a comedy western about  the first Black sheriff in the west. Do you know who played the role of Sheriff Bart?", "correct_answer": "Cleavon Little", "incorrect_answers": ["Mel Brooks", "Pat McCormick", "Samuel Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the structure/statue in the film Cars, that McQueen dragged around town, ripping up the streets?", "correct_answer": "Stanley", "incorrect_answers": ["Stanford", "Billy Joe", "Bob"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dead Presidents, what part of his body did Jose lose while serving as a demolition expert in the war?", "correct_answer": "hand", "incorrect_answers": ["arm", "leg", "foot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Canadian, born in 1954, directed Terminator.", "correct_answer": "James Cameron", "incorrect_answers": ["Ridley Scott", "John Carpenter", "Brian de Palma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kelevra, the last name of the protagonist in Lucky Number Slevin, roughly translated in Hebrew means good cat.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This progressive generative disease of the brain results in loss of cognitive ability and uncontrolled movements, called chorea, the Greek word for dance.", "correct_answer": "Huntingtons Disease", "incorrect_answers": ["Alzheimers Disease", "Myasthenia Gravis", "Multiple Sclerosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a person bought a 5.05 acre tract, how many square feet would be in the 5.05 acre tract?", "correct_answer": "219,978", "incorrect_answers": ["217,800", "217,500", "219,675"]}]